The correct answer as to whether you need to create any additional variables
Правильный ответ - надо ли создавать еще переменные -
is, well, no.
это - нет.
You have a variable keeping track of Team A's score.
У вас есть переменная в которой хранится счет Команды А.
These two buttons are simply going to affect the value
Эти две кнопки простоменяют значение хранящееся
that's stored in that score, and there's no other variables that are needed.
значение счета и для этого не нужны другие переменные.
Alright, let's see what this looks like in code.
Итак, посмотрим на код.
We can actually model this pretty closely from off of what we did for
Мы можем смоделировать все из того что ранее сделали для
addThreeForTeamA.
addThreeForTeamA.
Whoops. I see a little error.
Ой, а вот и небольшая ошибка.
Let's add a space here.
Добавим пробел.
Sorry, where was I?
Итак, о чем это я?
Yes, we can do the same thing for one and two as we did for three.
Мы можем сделать для один и два то же что делали для три.
In fact, I don't like typing.
На самом деле я не люблю печатать.
I'm going to just go ahead and copy this.
Я собираюсь просто скопировать.
And I'll paste it here, in the addTwoForTeamA and
И вставить вот сюда, в addTwoForTeamA и
here in the addOneForTeamA.
и сюда в addOneForTeamA.
Okay.
Ладно.
So now for example, in addTwoForTeamA, it's adding three to the score and
Итак, например, в addTwoForTeamA, три добавляется к счету и
then displaying the score.
отображает счет.
But I don't want it to add three, I want it to add two.
Но мне не надо чтобы добавлялось три, я хочу добавить два.
And here, in addOneForTeamA It's adding 3 to the score, but
А зжесь, в addOneForTeamA, к счету добавляется три, но
I actually just wanted to add 1.
мне надо просто добавить 1.
But in both cases, I still wanted to display the score.
Но в обеих случая мне надо, чтобы отображался счет.
I'm just changing it by a little bit of a different number.
Я просто меняют все на другое число.
Let's run this to see if it works.
Теперь прогоним и посмотрим -
Okay, moment of truth.
работает ли. Момент истины -
Okay, looks like it's working.
кажется, работает.